# Hi, my name is Henya Adler I'm looking for UX/UI Designer



### Contact me

+972 58 778 2 776 henyadesign@gmail.com www.henya.me LinkedIn Facebook

### **Skills**

After Effects Photoshop Premier Pro Illustrator

XD

InDesign

Figma

Wordpress

**HTML** 

CSS

# Languages

Hebrew English

Ukrainian

Russian

Spanish

# **Projects**

Books exchange app

Conference website

I'm a highly skilled and versatile designer with experience in designing, animating, branding, prototyping, and basic coding. I specialize in creating user-friendly designs and am committed to improving the user experience through user research, simplification, and visual design. Overall, my passion for design and my commitment to improving the user experience drive me to continuously improve my skills and expertise.

## **Experience**

### **Marketing Designer**

**Castro-Hoodies** 

March 2022 - Present

- Designed ads, banners, newsletters.
- Designed brand identity.
- Created animations and videos.
- Redesigning from scratch e-commerce websites.

### **UX/UI** Designer

**Rom Marketing** 

January 2020 - February 2022

- Designed wireframes and UI.
- Designed brand identity.
- Created animations and videos.

### **Graphic Designer**

**Nail Pharm** 

July 2017 - December 2019

- Developed and perfected skills in marketing, branding, and other areas.
- Delivered advertising materials for social media, banners, print and packaging materials.

### **Graphic Design - Freelance**

Henya Design

2017 - 2022

- Created brand identity.
- Created print materials.
- Created Wordpress websites using Elementor/ Gutenberg.

### Education

### **UX/UI** Design

Netcraft academy 2020 - 2021

### **Graphic Design**

Shenkar Handesaim 2016 - 2017

### **Advertising & Brand Communication (B.A.)**

MEGI Institute

2009 - 2014